Guide to the Office of Facilities, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Facilities, Yale University, records
1868-1990
RU 8
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
83.5
The records consist of project files of the Director of Facilities Construction Organization and requests for service documenting the activities of the Yale Office of Facilities.
Yale University. Office of Facilities
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of project files of the Director of Facilities Construction Organization and requests for service documenting the activities of the Yale Office of Facilities.
College buildings -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Maintenance and repair; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Office of Facilities
- Engineering Service Requests and operating manuals, circa 1968-1989; Accession 1990-A-097
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 2, 2024
  - Engineering Service Requests
    - 102-439 (Box 1)
    - 464-1081 (Box 2)
    - 1118-2981 (Box 3)
    - 3105-3491 (Box 4)
    - 3492-5019 (Box 5)
    - 5024-6901 (Box 6)
    - 10060-20706 (Box 7)
  - Operating manuals (Box 8)
  - Operating manuals (Box 9)
- Estimated Service Requests (ESR) and director and project manager files, circa 1930-1990; Accession 1993-A-038
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - ESR 3663-3715 (Box 29)
  - ESR 3716-3793 (Box 30)
  - ESR 3847-3890 (Box 32)
  - ESR 3891-5057 (Box 33)
  - ESR 6005-8107 (Box 35)
  - ESR 20000-20089 (Box 36)
  - ESR 20090-20187 (Box 37)
  - ESR 20288-20364 (Box 39)
  - ESR 20426-20515 (Box 41)
  - ESR 20577-20655 (Box 43)
  - ESR 20656-20754 (Box 44)
  - ESR 0185-0319 (Box 1)
  - ESR 0388-0424 (Box 3)
  - ESR 0424-0452 (Box 4)
  - ESR 0491-0528 (Box 6)
  - ESR 0529-0540 (Box 7)
  - ESR 0541-0568 (Box 8)
  - ESR 0756-0763 (Box 13)
  - ESR 0764-0824 (Box 14)
  - ESR 0825-0891 (Box 15)
  - ESR 0914-0978 (Box 17)
  - ESR 0979-01264 (Box 18)
  - ESR 01774-01838 (Box 19)
  - ESR 01839-2513 (Box 20)
  - ESR 2513-2513 (Box 21)
  - ESR 2513-2668 (Box 22)
  - ESR 2922-2999 (Box 24)
  - ESR 3374-3529 (Box 25)
  - ESR 3530-3572 (Box 26)
  - ESR 3572-3616 (Box 27)
  - ESR 3617-3662 (Box 28)
  - ESR 0319-0387 (Box 2)
  - ESR 0453-0491 (Box 5)
  - ESR 0568-0631 (Box 9)
  - ESR 0632-0678 (Box 10)
  - ESR 0678-0715 (Box 11)
  - ESR 0716-0756 (Box 12)
  - ESR 0891-0913 (Box 16)
  - ESR 2674-2921 (Box 23)
  - ESR 3794-3846 (Box 31)
  - ESR 5058-600435 (Box 34)
  - ESR 20188-20287 (Box 38)
  - ESR 20364-20425 (Box 40)
  - ESR 20515-20576 (Box 42)
  - Graduate Off-Campus Housing (FiH Comittee), 0 (Box 45)
  - Alternative Housing 1973, 0 (Box 45)
  - Housing- Whitney Colleges: Cost-Budget-Commercial 1971-73, HLH27- Hillhouse Ave, 27: Economic 1977 (Box 45)
  - Housing- Whitney Colleges: Program, Schedule, Miscellaneous1968-73, Growth Center (Box 45)
  - SNET Co. Parking Garage 1970-71 (Box 45)
  - Yale- Overall Parking Needs 1967-71, 0 (Box 45)
  - Music Center Budget 1973-75, 0 (Box 45)
  - Trinity Church Parish House 1979, 0 (Box 45)
  - Parking- Yale 1967-70 (Box 45)
  - PSPS- Pierson-sage Parking: Program, etc. 1971-75, 0 (Box 45)
  - YUAG- Yale U. Art Gallery: Ordway Collection 1980 (Box 45)
  - Advisory Committee on Band G- New Haven Preservation Trust Data 1972-74,1978, 0 (Box 45)
  - A amp; A- Art and Architecture Building: fire repairs 1969-71, 0 (Box 45)
  - TRUM85- 85 Trumbull st: Consilium 1977, 0 (Box 45)
  - HLH27- Hillhouse Ave, 27: Economic Growth Center 1977, 0 (Box 45)
  - DL Dunham Lab: Alterations- Phase 3, 0 (Box 45)
  - DL Dunham Lab: Alterations- Phase 1, 0 (Box 45)
  - Band G General Background Data 1962-76, 0 (Box 45)
  - Grove-Whitney Proposals 1980 (Box 45)
  - Arts Area Expansion 1979-1980 (Box 45)
  - Psychology and Related Moves, 0 (Box 45)
  - PARK217-Park st, 217: Phi Gamma Alpha, 1967-68 (Box 45)
  - PARK218-Park st, 218, 1968 (Box 45)
  - PROS400-Prospect st, 400, 1970 (Box 45)
  - Psychology and Related Moves, 1973-74 (Box 45)
  - SHM-Sterling Hall of Medicine: Cll Wing Renovation-Accounts ", 1969 (Box 46)
  - Re: Coeducation -Estimate Budgets Renovations for, 1969 (Box 46)
  - Cancer Center Project-Cedar st. Bridge, Hunter Bldg. Addition-Winchester Renovation-George E. Fuller Co. Estimate, 1977-78 (Box 46)
  - Index of General Contractors and Subcontractors, 1934? (Box 46)
  - Instructions for Air Raid Shelters, 1945? (Box 46)
  - A amp; A-Art and Architecture Building: Progess Photos, 1964 (Box 46)
  - SML-CCL Cross Campus Library: Job Meetings (DM Hummel), 1969-70 (Box 46)
  - SML Annex-Health center: Cash Flow Projected, 1969-70 (Box 46)
  - Cancer Genetics, 1974-76 (Box 47)
  - Child study Center, 1974-75 (Box 47)
  - C Wing-Cell Biology, 1974-75 (Box 47)
  - Library storage-Mudd, 1976-1980 (Box 47)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 47)
  - campaign for Yale, 1975-76 (Box 47)
  - A amp; A-Art and Architecture Repair, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Band G Notes-General, 1966-76 (Box 47)
  - Minutes-Building and Grounds Corporation Committee, 1978 (Box 47)
  - Minutes-Building and Grounds Corporation Committee, 1976-77 (Box 47)
  - Havermeyer House Preservation Trust, 1975 (Box 47)
  - Institute of Sacred Music, 1974-79 (Box 47)
  - Holiday Inn, 1969-73 (Box 47)
  - University Buildings-Miscellaneous, 1975-79 (Box 47)
  - Berkeley Divinity School-Social Science Relocation, 1971-73 (Box 47)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Center, 1976-79 (Box 47)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Center, 1969-70 (Box 47)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Center, 1970-75 (Box 47)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Gallery, 1968-69 (Box 47)
  - Housing-Undergraduate, 1971-78 (Box 47)
  - school of Organization and Development, 1976-1980 (Box 47)
  - Yale Buildings-Gross Sq. Feet and Cubic Feet, 1930-44 (Box 48)
  - Design Standards for Materials-Notes to Bidders, 1930-39 (Box 48)
  - Statistics on the Yale Campus Bldgs.Location, Architect, Material, Area, Date of Beginning-Completion, Costs (To Ostrander from Francis), 1930-34 (Box 48)
  - Yale Building Costs-Detailed Accounts, 1928-40 (Box 48)
  - Yale Building Costs-Detailed Accounts, 1928-40 (Box 48)
  - Yale Building Costs-Cubic costs, Cube and Ground Area, Budgets, 1930-40 (Box 48)
  - General Planning Schedule-Long Range Planning, 1967, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Yale City Planning Problems, 1970-74 (Box 49)
  - Music School studies, 1978 (Box 49)
  - WLH-WML Harkness Hall: Basement Renovation, Payroll, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Social Science MAC, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Psychology and Related Moves, 1973-74 (Box 49)
  - Social Science Center-Space, 1971 (Box 49)
  - MUDD-Mudd Library Space, 1977 (Box 49)
  - (Major) Planning Considerations, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Berkeley-Social Science Costs, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Berkeley Divinity, 1970-71 (Box 49)
  - Band G-general (Dunn), 1978 (Box 49)
  - Music Center-Site and Elizabeth Club, 1973-75 (Box 49)
  - Elizabethan Club (Dunn), 1974-75 (Box 49)
  - Music Center, 1969-75 (Box 49)
  - Music Center-Budget, 1972-75 (Box 49)
  - Music Center-Garage, 1974-78 (Box 49)
  - BAC-British Art Gallery, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Psychology Moves, 1973-78 (Box 49)
  - Oak street Connector, 1972 (Box 49)
  - SOMDH-SaM Dining Hall, 1977-78 (Box 49)
  - SOMDH-SOM Dining Hall: Zoning Variance, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Social Service Center, 1968-71 (Box 50)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Center: Original Plan-Scrapped, 1969-71 (Box 50)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Center and Art Gallery: security, 1970-71 (Box 50)
  - BAC-British ArBudgets t Center-Mellon Center:, 1970-71 (Box 50)
  - City Ordinance-Judge Thim Report, 1969 (Box 50)
  - PROS140-Prospect st, 140: Social Science Library, 1976-77 (Box 50)
  - SLB-sterling Law BLDGS: Law School Lecture Room: Alterations, 1978 (Box 50)
  - SOMDH-SOM Dining Hall: Expansion, 1977 (Box 50)
  - Norfolk-Housing Studies-Yale Summer School of Music and Art, undated (Box 50)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Center: Cost study Mail, 1971 (Box 50)
  - Engineer Applied Science program Cost, 1965-67 (Box 50)
  - American Art-McNiel, 1974-76 (Box 50)
  - Garvin Alteration in Art Gallery, 1967-70 (Box 50)
  - Yale Psychiatric Institute, 1971 (Box 50)
  - Holiday Inn-etc. 1973, 1973-75 (Box 50)
  - BAC-British Art Center-Mellon Centerzoning, 1972-77 (Box 50)
  - Math Building-Competition, 1969-70 (Box 50)
  - ML-Mason Lab-E and AS-Alterations, 1964-68 (Box 50)
  - Becton-Becton E amp; AS Center 1965-69 (Box 50)
  - ELM149-ELM st, 149: (ALT for Admissions) 1980-1982 (Box 51)
  - Divinity Library Alterations, 1973-1981 (Box 51)
  - Handicap Access, 1977-1982 (Box 51)
  - YORK212-York st, 212: Zeta Psi-DKE, 1973-75 (Box 51)
  - SCL-sterling Chern Lab-Long Range Renovation Projects, 1978-1982 (Box 51)
  - Main Campus Overall Parking, 1974-77 (Box 51)
  - SOM School of Organization and Management, 1977-78 (Box 51)
  - Central Operations Facility, 1981 (Box 51)
  - Space Planning, 1982 (Box 51)
  - Davies-Davies House, 1978-79 (Box 51)
  - SCUP, 1973-74, 1978,1981 (Box 51)
  - TEMP405-Temple st, 405, 1978 (Box 51)
  - UT-university Theater, 1979-1981 (Box 51)
  - WALL53-Wall st,53, 1979-1980 (Box 51)
  - Math Building, 1970, 1974-75 (Box 51)
  - Buildings (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1979-1983 (Box 51)
  - YU Guidebook, 1980-1983 (Box 51)
  - Band G Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 51)
  - Capital Projects (miscellaneous), 1975-1981 (Box 51)
  - Capital Construction-Planning Budgets, 1970-1982 (Box 51)
  - WALL53-Wall st,53: Final Accounting, 1981 (Box 51)
  - Space Allocation, 1966-69/1982 (Box 51)
  - WALL53- Wall st/ 53: Trinity Auditorium 1980 (Box 51)
  - WALL53- Wall st/ 53: Trinity Parish- New 1979-1981, 0 (Box 51)
  - Assignments, 0 (Box 51)
  - WALL53- Wall st/ 53: Trinity Parish- 1973, 0 (Box 51)
  - Humanities Institute, 0 (Box 51)
  - WALL53- Wall st/ 53: Auditorium Seating 1981, 0 (Box 51)
  - G. stevens - Peabody - Exchange of Space 1979, 0 (Box 51)
  - WALL53- Wall st/ 53: Trinity Parish 1979, 0 (Box 51)
  - PROS140- Prospect st/ 140: Social 1974-77 (Box 51)
  - Science Library, 0 (Box 51)
  - YRT- Yale Repertory Theater 1974-75, 0 (Box 51)
  - Real Estate 1981-1982, 0 (Box 51)
  - HGS- Hall of Graduate Studies: Survey 1968, 0 (Box 51)
  - JE- Jonathan Edwards College: survey 1967-69, 0 (Box 51)
  - CC- Calhoun College: survey 1967-68, 0 (Box 51)
  - DC- Davenport College: survey 1967-68, 0 (Box 51)
  - PC- Pierson College: survey 1967-68, 0 (Box 51)
  - SM- Silliman College: survey 1967-68, 0 (Box 51)
  - Revised Sheets- Reidential Colleges 1969, 0 (Box 51)
  - SLB- sterling Law Buildings: Survey 1968, 0 (Box 51)
  - JE-Jonathan Edwards college: Master Copy 1969, 0 (Box 51)
  - Residential colleges- single Rooms Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Extra Copies- Letters and Exhibits First Issue, 1969 (Box 51)
  - BK-Berkeley College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - BR-Branford College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - CC-Calhoun College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - DC-Davenport College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - TD-Timothy Dwight College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - MC-Morse College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - PC-Pierson college: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - SC-Saybrook college: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - SM-Silliman College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - ES-Ezra Stiles College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - TC-Trumbull College: Master Copy, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Extra Copies-college Plans in Color, 1969 (Box 51)
  - ES-Ezra Stiles College: survey, 1967-68 (Box 51)
  - MC-Morse College: survey, 1967-68 (Box 51)
  - SC-Saybrook College: survey, 1967-68 (Box 51)
  - BR-Branford College: survey, 1967-68 (Box 51)
  - TD-Timothy Dwight College: survey, 1967-68 (Box 51)
  - BK-Berkeley college: survey, 1967-68 (Box 51)
  - BRBL-Beineke Rare Book Library, 1963 (Box 52)
  - BRBL-Beineke Rare Book and Main Library, 1961 (Box 52)
  - Parking-YPA, operations, Miscellaneous, 1967-73 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence, 0 (Box 52)
  - YSN-Yale School of Nursing, 1975 (Box 52)
  - Old Campus Budget, 1976 (Box 52)
  - Old Campus, 1976 (Box 52)
  - GA Fuller- Old Campus, 1975 (Box 52)
  - Old Campus Renovations, 1974 (Box 52)
  - BAC- British Art Center Correspondence 1973-1980 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Univ. Health Center: Job Meetings 1971, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Univ. Health Center 1968, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Univ. Health Center: utility Costs 1979, 0 (Box 53)
  - CCL- Cross Campus and UHSC- Health Center 1971, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Univ. Health Center: Sub-Contractors 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Communications 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Temperature Controls 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Budgets 1971, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Bids 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - (Mechanics and Electrics), 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Bidders 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Univ. Health Center: Letters of Intent 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Railroad Problems 1968, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Interior Furnishings 1968, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Construction Bids 1968, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC- Dniv. Health Center: Constructor Contract 1969, 0 (Box 53)
  - UHSC-Univ. Health Center: Budget DataFuller summaries, 1968-69 (Box 53)
  - BAC-British Art Center, 1975-1980 (Box 53)
  - GBH Macomber, 1974-1983 (Box 53)
  - SML-CCL-Cross Campus: Contracts, 1967 (Box 53)
  - CCL-Cross Campus: Water-Proof Problem, 1975 (Box 53)
  - Parking Reference Material, 1967-70 (Box 54)
  - PSpp-Pierson-Sage Power: Pierson-sage Boiler and AC Plant, 1961-63 (Box 54)
  - SML-sterling Memorial Library Annex, 1969 (Box 54)
  - WHIT33-Whitney Avenue/ 33, 1965 (Box 54)
  - Medical Center Zoning, 1970-71 (Box 54)
  - High and Wall streets Project, 1961-64 (Box 54)
  - Dixwell Avenue, 1960-61 (Box 54)
  - General-High l Wall/ Dixwell etc. Redevelopment Proposals, 1961 (Box 54)
  - Hospital Block-Planning Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1961-62 (Box 55)
  - Medical Center Review-Row Committee Report" ", 1964 (Box 55)
  - Medical School-Long Range Planning, 1964-65 (Box 55)
  - Parking Medical Center (Early Schemes Reports), 1965-69 (Box 55)
  - Medical Center Planning Committee, 1967-71 (Box 55)
  - BB Boardman Building: Committee Proposed Changes, 1971 (Box 55)
  - BB Boardman Building: Completion 3rd and 4th Floor, 1971 (Box 55)
  - LSOG-Lab for SURG/OB/GYN: Revised, 1974 (Box 55)
  - Medical School-Child study Center, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Yale Psychiatric Institute, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Grace Educational Building-Psychiatry, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Hughes Medical School Institute, 1978 (Box 55)
  - SMH: Sprague Memeorial Hall, 1980-1984 (Box 56)
  - SML-Sterling Memorial Library: Buttress, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
  - SML-Sterling Memorial Library: Electrical, 1981 (Box 56)
  - SML-Sterling Memorial Library: Entrance, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
  - SML-Sterling Memorial Library: Stained Windows, 1931-34 (Box 56)
  - SSS-Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall, 1980 (Box 56)
  - STOECK-Stoeckel Hall, 1983-1984 (Box 56)
  - TD-Timothy Dwight College, 1980-1983 (Box 56)
  - JE-Jonathan Edwards college: Weir Hall, 1982-1983 (Box 56)
  - WHIT175, Whitney Ave, 175, 1983-1984 (Box 56)
  - YORK149, York st, 149: Mechanical, 1982-1983 (Box 56)
  - YORK149, York st, 149, 1980-1983 (Box 56)
  - YALEBOWL-Yale Bowl, undated (Box 56)
  - Cahn Building survey Legal Contracts and Agreements, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
  - BECTON-Becton E amp; AS Center ESR 0918 (2 folders), 1986-1987 (Box 56)
  - BECTON-Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
  - BECTON-Architect's Supplemental Instructions, 1987 (Box 56)
  - BECTON-Job Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
  - BECTON-Proposed Changes, 1986-1989 (Box 57)
  - BECTON-Proposal Requests, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - BECTON-Change Orders, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - -BECTON-Transmittals (2 folders), 1986 (Box 57)
  - BECTON-Shop Drawings, 1986 (Box 57)
  - DL-Dunham Lab: Invoices, Purchase Orders, 1986 (Box 57)
  - DL-Dunham Lab: 1st Floor, 1986 (Box 57)
  - DL-Dunham Lab: Requests 1st Floor Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - DL-Dunham Lab: 1st Floor Minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 57)
  - DL-Dunham Lab: 1st Floor, 1986 (Box 57)
  - DW-Dwight Hall Chapel, 1981 (Box 57)
  - BR-Branford College: Harkness Tower, 1987 (Box 57)
  - BECTON-Becton E amp; AS Center, 1987 (Box 57)
  - PC-Pierson College: Library, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - YALEBOWL-Yale Bowl Press, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - YALEBOWL-Yale Bowl, 1984 (Box 57)
  - DW-Dwight Hall Chapel, 1986 (Box 57)
  - PC-Pierson college, 1986 (Box 57)
  - John Canning Restoration Painting, 1987 (Box 57)
  - MUDD-Mudd Library: Roofing, 1986 (Box 57)
  - PARK211-Park st, 211, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Golf Course Irrigation (2 folders), 1985 (Box 57)
  - John Martin-structural Engineer-Cook Boat House, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
  - Donald Baerman, Restoration Archt., 1981-1983 (Box 57)
  - Cimino-Harkness Masonry Work, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
  - Contractor Files-Jeter, Cook, Jepson; E amp; F; Roth amp; Moore, Archt; Ken Rich, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
  - Hendry Hall Roof Survey and Misc., 1981-1983 (Box 58)
  - BECTON-Becton E amp; AS Center: Generator Emergency, 1987 (Box 58)
  - COXE-Coxe Cage, 1985-1987 (Box 58)
  - COXE-Coxe Cage Surfacing, 1981-1982 (Box 58)
  - A amp; A-Art and Architecture, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - YUAG-Yale Univ. Art Gallery, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
  - YUAG-Yale Univ. Street Bridge Art Gallery and High, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - BECTON, 1981-1983 (Box 58)
  - BRBL-Beineke Library, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
  - BRBL-Beineke Library: Sealant, 1982-1985 (Box 58)
  - COOKBH-Cook Boathouse, 1981-1983 (Box 58)
  - COXE-Coxe Cage, 1980-1983 (Box 59)
  - CRWN30S-Crown st, 305, 1980-1981 (Box 59)
  - MDN-Main Dining Hall-University Dining Halls, 1980-1981 (Box 59)
  - UHSC-Univ. Health Center ( 2 folders), 1980-1982 (Box 59)
  - BR-Branford College: Harkness Tower, 1980-1981 (Box 59)
  - BR-Branford College: Harkness Tower, 1981-1982 (Box 59)
  - BR-Branford College: Harkness Tower, 1982-1983 (Box 59)
  - HH-Hendrie Hall, 1980-1982 (Box 59)
  - JESFC-JE Smilow Field Ctr: Lapham Field House, 1980-1981 (Box 59)
  - SLB-Sterling Law Bldgs., 1980-1983 (Box 59)
  - SLB-sterling Law Bldgs.: Roof, 1984 (Box 59)
  - Me & ES-Morse College and Ezra Stiles College, 1982 (Box 59)
  - WNSL-Wright Nuclear structure Lab, 1982 (Box 59)
  - OML-Osborn Memorial Lab; Burton and Van Houten, 1980-1982 (Box 59)
  - PWG-Payne Whitney Gym, undated (Box 59)
  - BBC-Brady-Boardman Connector: Fuller Estimate (2 folders), 1970 (Box 59)
  - PM-Peabody Museum, 1982 (Box 59)
  - PM-Peabody Museum, 1981, 1983 (Box 59)
  - A. H. Reise Daily Appointments, 1967-1992 (Box 60)